when i get that she is selfish good for children
and how to sell i sat at fat fat going
to nat after that shit announced yet these to dinky
tariff she is tasty view processed and all that intelligent
he has set up and tell it yeah i know
that her son cost weekend edition
and today is a very special day and one that
brings us all together to celebrate national literacy awareness week
and i'm delighted that to be a wrist rest of
the fat and here in our civil trial she gave
rest of mission to the importance of space walk to
kind fate feast be taken off to a national education
c. agents say and i acting
the agency be such an important vital resource for haiti
goes to experiencing interested challenges
and to your car think the world's hope and overture
she's too so many citizens and chirping carnage purchase page
and i think in fact when you're extending citizenship and
the pulse of issues his citizenship to so many people
and particularly those who for any one of the number
of reasons may have been deprived of stuff which are
nation off itchy kingfisher c skins missionary year period of thereabouts
i think it experiencing interested difficulties he can
creation of an atmosphere that is doctor noted for so
many people have one particular day to welcome those who
have taken on the chapter for tracy kids and whipping
cherie there's cops and with our thoughts and it's going
to be such a profit asap i think that matching form
and the fisher says is a journey into the night
and went out the key changes wants that
they many years ago when i was in my life
as a politician time member having a great friend of
mine who paul cox is an ancient and a day
after he knows he's at the flavor for friends and
to all foxes and train them best for our sense
of having to work that doesn't have a caller this
issue an end to the tiller may cali manage change
in a trench he used to it off to the
coin wound around the same route that antique in a
bad one knowing when to turn off and he brought
his grandson with it and a grandson which in fact
a tentative f. which makes it tougher to take from
that from the round up and haiti at my great
friend aflatoxin who was one of the fox peter he
says shocked of farcical do you eat through c. corwin
was of great assistance to and it was a life
changing experience as it is for everyone but each and
every one of you i've been looking at the de
dios was an immense just picture shared your great inspiration
to others he says it's a very difficult and eighty
take sit back and precincts act of carnage to actually
stepped forward and say i'm going to change this aspect
of my life so i want to come into for
your car eight hundred to terminate the day i was
in the detainees over there and have us just looking
at in a particular story for example and before us
today and when he described for us to form a
pinky psychiatrist chartered and his journey toward the national debt
to new jersey agency's work i think it's very very
very moving and to keep the change honest to the
treaty emaciated shouldn't speak to an describing something that is
not easy for anyone to do this it's a shame
frustration and failure to preaching difficulties creation for him was
deeply moving as these basics strong sentence that is so
subtle now he said he wanted to be at the
ramada for his chicken and to be a bit to
purchase a page engage patron and i think that all
of those stories which of necessity that derek's on the street
off peak of taken current trends will persevere to the
face it difficult to
acting he's willing to succeed is apocalypse just for anyone
who may feed his car if i might just it
was another group of peter the dead man or third
week from my tribe made a gingrich presented peeping cope
with this for some others to the trapping communication was
going to prison and actually know from my visits to
christmas when that many people would tend to prison unfortunately
a pediatrician came out from the pendant and in fact
at cheating you sure ceased its is part of being
a good to protect herself back and put then moving
on and get to purchase of haiti and i think
it's windows and who worked with cactus renaud try would
acknowledge the role that the life recently and how hedge
funds if they have peed in in promotion dispute silicone
of those who have shared destroy our commander car and
i have seen that you're doing so in the public
that we had great chiles and his statement that is
often lasting peace from coming forward can't take heed of
her servant to fit the as what is that there's
a very cold fish between each receive difficulties and marginalization
any cooperation disenfranchisement and so she's just an a. in
fact we must remember this invitation to participation of ocean
system itself at such a tentative to produce association it
but i think you
oh
to know what the people affected asian and the sense
of possibilities extraordinary moment in each one of the buyout
of fate that people say i can do with aids
and ashes enables them to move on to wash is
not just the acquisition of his skin bush indictment and impala
a nobody
itchy finger over usury see he's one of the sestanovich
and colas and that would be a very important of
contribution to sustain the development and production of philpot pauper
to also it's something important to realize his plan and
i was associated with such massive could be kissed chief
mendez think in any one country would it be in
the period of an estella and chip from and the
captain and ingenious correct one where the unesco walked to
the reduction of people for it or who suffer you
should say it was the most significant of any particular
country in nashua seven nineteen eighties bracken tenuous would've th
even sadder than gripping under repair in his grasp and
connections breathtaking pace and a woman who was in charge
of the border post was so struck by her new
big issue to reach if she she did she insisted
on reaching out the f. train left in its twitter
admission at elizabeth arden half a mind of a film
as somebody had to say the gate you might just
concentration that paragraphs about the bennett pay for it what
it was the sense of excitement and joanie be actually
now the bit to you was sold these black sweep
them and actually air ticket that i sold that and
that huge changes made and of course is that they
should not just trade deficits purchase patient society with a
cleaner member when the treasure to be attached to sell
the gulf war and it was because if people didn't
get purchase a patient and wanted justice and they want
to security for their families and they wanted a different
forms of that i can figure it out and we
have made great extent advances in relation to add to
his trusted with where warsaw front back and many of
the country senior which one in fine i think dishes
on a recent early c. p. seventy one in six
either shadows are african who won and if you want
on if i could finish receipts k. so that is
much to be done packing fish in the hat i
think that connection and his new three c. agencies campaigns
and i'm fact that it's getting recognition to take the
first to campaign had the general faster progress that are
very very important i've no doubt that these initiatives we'd
be instrumental in changing eventually see key figure i spoke
to an awesome uncle to the irish leaching association of
fact and i quote that time the rights that great
champion of civil rights frederick douglass when he said when
you learn to read to you in the spring for free
pat i'll trail off to talk about your past couple
of the defense beaches atkinson and one separate and different
cases in a very trying to save this to leech
into to swim and have access to a musical instrument
you to connor now waitress creations this basic security for
a finite we could take douglas's wives when you learn
to read you would be free for free except a
hot ticket to journey to a knife and reading is when
hey it's i'm optimistic that you would never be known
and i am re reading is fundamental and it's it
gives great pleasure pleasure was fond of megatron independence and
our sense of where you'd be initially so they gave
us a bed and asked
the capacity for reflection and decline in some perspective
the chain trusting when the debate came about the printing
press farce and peeters said
sure drinks didn't the capacity to reach him and when
the opponents such difficulties people enough don't you read the
bible of henry tom pains path it says when i
think there should a week the piece of fundamental to
democracy and new jersey was what made possible the practice
patient classes of different and to end the end excluded
groups in the town in maine to process it says
in the digital age and i know that madame have
now and has extended detected a faint c. it's part
of the campaign and eastern pimple i have to say
my sense that i want trip to the testing carnage
institutions and i'm hgh calm to all particular day off
piece that we have our order and people who were
experiencing difficulty in addition to teach it to shirts hey
if you make no effort to kato had said to
be to make the transition you were abusive to check
out to have a payoff maybe one of the disappointing
features an all of a institution behavior is not bad
is there is room for consent have talked lately he's
been speaking to each and it changed in the last
couple of decades and there's an enormous value and people
visit this country no such thing peter spoken to which
could send care compassion and kindness i think and that's
where off and teach it to intercede group would be
very very important i sold great shakes afterthought indiana islands
in any sheerer every young peter where in fact show
and giving people excuse to some of their grandparents and
aunts and the older people where sharing the heritage of
the ion and the result of us at painful cuts
both generations ever hit the h. i. and having knowlton
inter generational conflict is a fantastic attracted to that the
more fifth generation say to speak to each other better
society is allied to finish by making one about myself
about eight o'clock in new jersey i have been in
a number of speech is safely sunday and and change
defend that there's an exact same way as having seizures
say was important to purchase a patient who sugar process
that gave us parliament sent those two participation in having
fiske and economic interest
understanding boxes in fact happening in relation to options that
are justified to the faces of fiske imperatives of our
economic issues that he's going to be just as important
i think the issue if we were sharing if we
had widespread fiscal and economic measures that we would not
have the difficulties in the european street fish we have
at the present time exactly the same way as we
had abuses in any deeper period of beepers suggested that
the warrant the archer of the work itself in the
same way the notion that matter sexual competition for all
our citizens to understand is enough weight to send to
the crash excitement and therefore i think that that is
probably the next to the area to which he would
move and the archduke to do is to say is
this present economic issues and it has the capacity to
win the european sense christoph kimmich with european street and
his capacity international to enable us to provide new forms
of an open economics into new forms of connection between
econ actually it takes economy and society with import resupply
i want to be here as patron of now that
is to thank you all the work that truck to
lay at the two wish with the success as it
continues is minimal week to seoul korea quality of assault
on a precocious eon ox aqua fina had to close
we didn't hear from the seats on the did not
mention shouts of coaches fish that annabelle crushed to win
in a thin on the east kamali shapely rocks on
the vatican how can these cochran to make a short
piece death toll could you would hope we shall not
to thank you so much for coming to take the
chance of a pap