i hate i pray at a car at a dashing
and it may not only is it was that it
would be at a large and edited a book a
new threat not that he is aidid is yes and
i guess i'm not these cars shots the local needs
jacobi out following i guess he's pretty yea yea yea
dot yeah oscar at a militia all toshio hobart this
product or in a bit c. n. n. i must
say price of law i'm states response as the day
they because i wanted to go and see the horses
and out of my interview which are attracted a united
want to that exceeds caught the time from their forces
which have repeated eighty of all it's been said easily
bought but every time i come here to the valley
city and i'm at an offer that this year science
be an energy of losses caused the plowing and this here
with the weather
they told us that at a democrat and an bias
would no doubt school and as modern as to be
garrity he sees it that fit now intended to instruct
him county often in an active they viewed as it
moves so attractive that successful that last year it went
up to one hundred eighty cows of people are all
but the chain with all the towns that this year
a tennis will go where no idea and thousands i
think it's a disease it is has grown as you
just have a chat and saying it until not just
a messy mm that cognitive and farwell already been at
what is one of europe's back just outdoor events and
white cotton into existence that is any of america it's
an instant can reach out which comes almost all white
knights in after the contras that annie just don't get
cooperation of so many people thought that this is a
testament to the vibrancy any organize a state that that
is there a diamonds farming community so is the amount
is still don't have talked i want to congratulate and
tanks are all the neighboring farm estimate as to take
it that transformation of six hundred acres of farmland although
i'm told this morning it's the urges that mounted into
our hands farming capital city
at the time the lazy efforts of life and that
is him out this in incarnate all of us have
acted expensive and development of the event is doing is
it's not to mention to the day case evidence that
crowd associations are denied the sea
including it's a garza both on the diplomatic director for
decades and they may kill that crap had gave a
commitment from the organizing group bennett who is yet what
about all of us and which is it might fat
and why deprivation is an outgrowth of last year after
year economy and enjoy these days yet
and they have a lot of a corporation
while the crowd because of that got the dead many
probably organizations is i'll come to get any great act
of enthusiasm and cooperation to make is that of a possible
right that corporation is indecision parts of rural life
and i think you have created and says david the
championship making it the most important enjoy the separation of rhode island
what i did not ask next
and i knew it save it
the little bow
and you don't slap at cost billions because their farming
of nardone are holed by ozarks society
our landscapes are natural environment and our way of life
anything on his desk at the championships that falling
an annual pledge an easy call is so fidelity will
to our talents is easy
you got that guys thought that connects it with a
lot of communities and that it went on about that
very fast bra
and i didn't get writing these days there's senate race
in an adult which you're easy i want to say
is when did say heels of the profile role of
that crap hasn't found a safe in our society
ephemeral and it could be fully understood
now doctor rieders insane statistics on that alpha sector
indeed indicators of any importance in the important indicator what'd
they don't have money taking took on a young hawkins
that bombing as a way of life
about onassis' family farming
and it's still good does he need to have all
hate to see and that didn't get it so many young people
it's our money that can access our lasted eight sir
when all of that france has not only did not
it's awful insecurity and it's importance from generation to generation
but also that in that in no or understanding
that caused brought being close to sell it and those plants
given that in a way of life
it needs and arthur
he supports the generous standing
it needs good still set policies as well as economic crisis intervention
and i understand that i would be visited today
i'm activities it would be as that jackass
and that was preparing my notes
is that indebted to what they've been written by david matter
on the chances are not crazy glue and communities
that they had a lot of things that i'm not
that they use the national guards are dead two thousand and fifteen
that's all to get one thousand three
in fact article president where bomb ripped up
no environment because they didn't have an office hours studying
come to a farm are sprouts and aziz and who
did it eddie got promise that we can have found
is that the chair because they may not be viable
my mistake to sit as president of ireland filing past
to be supportive
as part of our economy yes they had records sector
these are not as they did to his industry
and it's contribution to the nation and overproduction of old
friend expanding population is significant and since it operates in
our world community is it provides elicited in cobb had
gone and what else it makes you is that accurate
happen or zeller says about about
get out from all the time then the end
our exports are hotter than sixty thousand jobs
i think that their contract has been and continues to
be sensitive issues beat out the future of our country
and our society are that it did begin i didn't
like it here is in and talking yet at the
dollar loss o'clock
party presented it in campaigns that are markedly the united kingdom
but i had seclusion elements in our society is about
your book although when you're up
an island is no exception and we essentially tracy says
that doesn't say he needs you and saturday in our
lives with sydney
offering a future for the next generation of educated young
farmers an average of kate said bright young farmers bali standouts
acknowledging these factors are quiet acknowledgment us at effect on
that road a box and that is the unbalanced nature
of development and arnett
that and that is developments is leaving us with a
role in the peace in some parts and then
also the oddest right of declined our been these economies
resides at the same calling stabbing at st films to
walk in advertising even more diamonds and make they can then
i also it affects the lives as i've billy zane
interest doctrine monet is crowded cities with inadequate therapist's hand
still showed lesions
which must be done what we all name far not
only had that europe and the walk out that means
that in athens the economy and society
and that he that he has to go when i
was starting house
what would it up to his belief is why we
and his garsten on me judaism and legion of many
it became a festival is manifest major
i didn't say to rodney king was predict what we
need to region and thinking and planning again
and when you're at a news is brought up with
an active adequate infrastructure
with an exodus of the armed people are now slowly
it's not being as good a job right names as
my own is is an asset was only by those
affected by for all of us
some of them voted to these days i regarded as an okay
because they are the agents and the cities and seventy
one president of all the jobs created by foreign direct
investment where a concentrated in existing craps crossed the widow's
club music charts in regard to sounds as guilty by
that i slept for walks phases where did kind is
taking place we had to be taking place before and
the recent census takers in two thousand and sixteen children
as in part to present our nectar divisions that cop
in asia blessing to try
this is something we have to address it creates apnea
it saddens our policy
in those areas as part of it as it is
one target by the farms where college economic mubarak there
are some new daughter possessed by an thousand psi see
if we didn't get their product and ruin the population
has consecrated in its reinforce by the loss of seven
cents status post office stops that house residence at that
i know those that is as an actor measures that day
i ask you as president to lead them back
u. s. has gained all the generations by then lied
to get the veterinarians annual it's to continue and anybody
that admits that thomas think crap
it was clearly is a nineteen days on the path
as a consensus oh
most of us notion infrastructure and i've been road you've
got the nation and vicious cycle
and i think it's the obvious what is the prize
is the intervention no maughan in relation to that sages
as dated say it applies the activity of enacted on
secretary of state
i think about artist made dad effects of this city
when the bluth max did seats back instead the city
plan to exoneration very serious than anticipated
i'll be inadequate service provision scholar that crowd get red
herrings that can see at about seven or that and
then of course there are other specific issues associated with
life in this city
spiraling costs associated with housing
and our associated with bullets speculation and to be added
a provision of housing on conservation disillusioned fragmentation
would yell at me that i denied today i want to say
we should try megan
the case that is there are patterns legion idea that
having a lot to make amends should she be at madison society
and the giants are providing and revitalizing rhode island
the n. not talking about it as a kind of
a case you have to respect the day that no
way of life
and it is tempting we eat
it's like a great challenges that are trying
it's one that can and must be next
can i take it as well
is that the the negatives about mars and venus griping
we have the means to science and technology and communications
to the jaw that the defense cuts is that outpaced
the thermal community and as a direct relationship between ronald
ronald b. is this promenade main infrastructure and was that be described
i didn't associate kite technology and science
crafted infrastructure expenditure of economic social and take it that time
and it has achieved our charts
an awesome by prince by you know it's a new
disease is not in evidence
it's not the result awesome natural phenomena as they did
a hideous some way of the work that jacket is
the case now and there is at it sounds as
nice and small
our fate has to make choices at human is effect
that the that'd be described
there are choices
there are fading and our state change
and we need to go we envision it imagination if
they don't be late bath
i think
something that's been parked
is that important that that then last thing we get
away from over to buy between city and caught
if there are problems in the wooten is in the
population yeah kind of easy to that problem is all
kinds population increase in the city and i'm making my
case i gain for me to that because by the
visiting our address is that in fact it's absolutely do
not plan by this thing and ruined infrastructure transport and
brought back by providing good business at all i get
a grasp that made a profit important for people to
go back again and a great flirting ignites the dullest
towns and villages where you see too many businesses fellas
got hump and added friend i felt as far as
the point of view
this is easily get it basically do that because they
only need aspiring india's economy and then i
in continue interaction between added run exchanges would be sustainable
yes it is next year at into the white sustained
did yeah marks the end of second anniversary of the
adoption of the two thousand and the sustainable development goal
when the great achievements of my time is present in
two thousand eighty to all our hearts need to we
have long asked him that he leads the of looked
in the economy
treads threads that ellis island i see that was then
that maybe late last week that natural why are animal
is that we've been asked to do is that they
get great go to our mad man and woman knows
that he can now and he lobbied the he says
the idea we have to do it if
that's that's where i says by the r. j. r.
our generation but the rule that the generations to come
and dole is both need all of our civil war
and it's good to see all the young people predicted
vichy year here i will take at least go and
make fill it in the giant no solid colors of
the apartment at x. good farming
that's a classic station and farm
that applies to you do now
between five and seven sons and daughters and maps and
i think that is that it is one of the
test of our time
you know when behind we will resume at that rate
by doesn't that mean then that the head of the
sector in agriculture must include although so far
and as latest project ten inches too
yes it is possible across the atlantic avenue to magic
kind yes sally management and that is as to the
great human energy
new policy to many spaceship many
education system that takes the concept of richness of their
own experience so sensitive and al at that he didn't
do was we say describing assets internationally in foreign policy
olive that mutating
must be beaten us thrown away and as artifacts an
item that is very improper
that's a one of the great successes when i go
to build a way that comes out
is the importance now that the text internationally and it's
going to be dead and that it's less as we
speak to retain i'll knock heads for that because her
projects face it is
but i do want to say this is way out
we need say today he not only in the projects
from full extent of the drug activity said we need
say sedated he's every stage of production at least at
safe and about to leave that the venue as haley
states to adapt to their weekend caught at it we
don't have a divinity
i had to that made with daddy by tuesday about
acting is largesse of all we said yesterday that just
makes it necessary to ensure that there are their transactions
between those who refuse bill to practice for the retail
sector and those who've been filled up one and i
think you fools wisely date sweetie pie has that
environment is as big a vision and economics as they
did anything anywhere and compliments it i'm one cabinet he
cheats at the expense of the yacht
i see a product that document going to these guys have budgets
iran great opportunity to send a great tradition not i'd
get a hat imagination and principally about farming sector and
i need we need to mobilize all of the madness
of our society in haiti the day that i can
describe believe him out of rotting food production we came
and carves out with a dish a new ideas you
escape and met with any bank that dennis franz had
any information and exchanging best practice at cross and major garrett
thought
out yeah they have pot belly like a means and
so on that in about two outfits that and that
is what is the day in part to easy so
much more than a sector and we have gone this
is one good example of federal programs that could or
boudreau grab the j. c. a different approach to fighting
and conservation from the ground up
analysts i want to see as as as well
a happier place for some animosity well if that is saying
wet blood stains that made a bayonet
i'm really implemented and a lady who after goldfarb
and i had id
we must don't cooperate in dealing with what it really
is not discuss and that is correct yes i think
we've lost that just getting into the rise in lagos
in fact it did in our maybe because of its
age of the cards i had talked to president of
bosnia as part of the advertising sector goes to the
united kingdom out
well is that all this
don't you consume irish film know that i guess in
the best quality hello dreyfus was held at all events
felt that while we have had faith that they've been
to get ready to costume with a sense to you
and i aced a seven and brought up and yet
we would go and find you laughed when we mistake
did your the markets we had and that's why i
think it's a vote that that meant as a key
in recognition of the vatican and eat about that in
every exit and go see it no we don't need
i have bought the only yes we do want to
see me about goldman and yet we want to attack
the state with sector that are very important to us
and they want the job done or not
and we always had from accept either and i want
to say to us president i'm in there would have
to have brought had it tastes enliven his accidents their
friendship extended towards island is alice who'll midwest
and it's not
sydney and i'm good at the invitation of batman
cedras may yet and you see the and i have
found that winning isn't the westcott
i did a little uneasy is as we get it
and these would provide opportunities for producers and ex parte
as abrogate the first to market for u. n. a
nice guy that our konzi's histories that kind of you
know we are and just make and economic tourism continent
and they didn't exist between our people back to abide
by the yen asked megan's back and then president of
the population poll indicates that and i said things that
i never easy thousand guys thought citizens
i've made os they in their home
and i must say that as well
and although technically easy sixty two
my grandfather's brother patrick and he says there may yet
integrated in amman very easy to go to queens that
by and by baghdad's was a seamstress but my grandmother's
brother tactic was a proud man
and is making on this it's this as a prop
and yeah i had said that you may make you
the one that crowding savages in queensland several times a
night since the day since it's the crap you know
i mean speaking of bodily senate is that they think
ye know them is that in red tape for us
as a doughnut but quite frankly
on saturday in europe
when we decided that we would be depended on us
think about ideal mach ten's world the da
that is why we're just not interested only in breaking
when it says is in the future of europe
i may heal up badly as security fat fat fat
mayonnaise and then the avi to make common cause with
all those all whacked at our initiative and you'll know
that from the twenty seven continents and that his party
theme parks and they say that the dosage they as
no reason to be naked to get his jack great
deal to pack
nanking economics and they speak on it to sell to
harness they need a genuinely know when the time
and offering the inoffensive zadeh data
you are about one strong nation is in our family
european union by you and say he stated that i
feel in any way to everyone at prospects and opportunities
to participate in family union and that is our sadness that far
i think now that he's not trying to read the
i. passionate barbara's iranian that hid millions activation path
it's a giant to radio energy the death threats that
there are estimates and did indeed get asked doctor is
it that was me that you
recognizing all that we poor as well as dole and
they did got tell it how in the cause of
the eighties that that day
it's great connected with redacting to wait so many out
people kind and hot as to where at different ages deadbeats together
said the guy that stands even from abroad is a
great makes statements are divided the a. c. r. b.
i'm speaker at as we've got to at this time around
got in and he out and shop
they see the c. s. senate end in a public
locally grown like saturday at our politics out of high
handed in teal is the senate telex crowding the ideas
that are set it is that said that a great
measure to i've been asked to play at the cases
that have had climbing seven cents off a sale but
that practice then added up